paullemberg.com 2014-11-22

# Paul Lemberg's Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy statement is for the following web sites:   

**www.paullemberg.com  
www.lemberg.com  
www.stratamax.com  
www.stratamaxresearch.com  
www.stratamax-research.com  
www.fasterchange.com  
www.quantumgrowthcoaching.com  
www.quantumgrowthcoachingfranchise.com  
www.earntwiceasmuchwithhalfthestress.com  
www.lemberg.com/faster.html **

Inventive Corporation, d/b/a Stratamax Research Institute, d/b/a Lemberg & Company, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the websites listed above. 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We may use cookies to save passwords so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites which are not owned or maintained by Lemberg & Company. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers) All ordering pages are on secure servers maintained by major hosting companies with extensive security measures. Lemberg & Company is not responsible for security breaches of these companies' servers. Lemberg & Company does not maintain any databases of Credit Card Numbers outside of these secure servers.. 

Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

Contacting the Web Site:  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Inventive Corporation  
PO Box 676173   
Rancho Santa Fe, CA 92067  
+1, 858-951-3055  
[  
Or contact us with this form](http://www.paullemberg.com/contact.html).
